<resources>
    <string name="app_name">VTubPedia</string>


    <string name="vtuber_name">vtuber name</string>
    <string name="agency">agency/perusahaan</string>
    <string name="description">Deskripsi</string>

    <string name="my_name">Yusman</string>
    <string name="my_email">yusmnn@gmail.com</string>

    <string name="twitter">(x)Twitter</string>
    <string name="linkedin">Linked In</string>
    <string name="github">Github</string>

    <string name="my_twitter">\@yusmnn</string>
    <string name="my_linkedin">\@yusmnn</string>
    <string name="my_github">\@yusmnn</string>

    <string name="profile">https://i.postimg.cc/VvcXBwGy/img-profile.jpg</string>


    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>Kobo Kanaeru</item>
        <item>Vestia Zeta</item>
        <item>Kaela Kovalskia</item>
        <item>Nekoyama Sena</item>
        <item>Ayunda Risu</item>
        <item>Moona Hoshinova</item>
        <item>IpoChan</item>
        <item>Mythia Batford</item>
        <item>Airani Iofifteen</item>
        <item>Aika Meru</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_agency">
        <item>Hololive</item>
        <item>Hololive</item>
        <item>Hololive</item>
        <item>Yume Reality</item>
        <item>Hololive</item>
        <item>Hololive</item>
        <item>Independen</item>
        <item>Independen</item>
        <item>Hololive</item>
        <item>Yume Reality</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="data_description">
        <item>
            Kobo Kanaeru (こぼ・かなえる) is a female Indonesian Virtual YouTuber associated with hololive, debuting as part of its Indonesian (ID) branch third generation of VTubers alongside Vestia Zeta and Kaela Kovalskia.\n\nA carefree girl who lives in the topmost room of a lighthouse, she is actually the bloodline of the strongest rain shaman in the area. She has great potential to control rain, but she does not like to do it as a task. In order to win back her Rain Master title, she needs to prove to her family that she can keep their rain shaman service afloat. Not only does she have to train daily, but she also needs to adopt some sort of virtual marketing strategy to succeed!.\n\nBecause of her short stature and immature mannerisms, Kobo initially projects the image of an endearing and energetic child with strange tendencies, though in reality she often acts like a sassy spoiled brat who frequently demands praises and playfully insults her peers and viewers and banters with them. She can very quickly lose her temper when enraged or provoked, and also gets flustered easily, particularly when being given genuine compliments or being called "princess." However, she can also be somewhat respectful of others, especially the ones she rarely interact with or personally idolised.\n\nShe is often considered one of the most "childlike" members of hololive that inspires others to pamper her like their little sister or daughter, although she is not above taking advantage of this to gain (often material) benefits. In spite of her childish "gremlin-like" attitude, not only is she tremendously talented and clever, but also capable of genuine sweetness when expressing her gratitude and happiness.\n\nHer somewhat clumsy English and weeb-level Japanese tends to project the image of an innocent, clumsy, and clueless child, yet those who understand Indonesian tend to understand her bratty mannerisms and profane language more. However, as she got more used to talking with her fellow members, the gap between the two has diminished.
        </item>
        <item>
            Vestia Zeta (ベスティア・ゼータ) is a female Indonesian Virtual YouTuber associated with hololive, debuting as part of its Indonesian (ID) branch third generation of VTubers alongside Kaela Kovalskia and Kobo Kanaeru.\n\nShe is the mysterious 7th recruit of The Secret Archive Unit that has a full license to collect virtual data.Despite her being a promising rookie, who is also known as codename V.7, she turns clumsy when things are not going exactly according to the manual.It was initially a lonely mission to infiltrate the virtual world, but now she had found comfort here. Will this mission end up leading her to a new destiny instead...?\n\nZeta adopts quite an adorable and curious personality similar to her favorite animal, cats. At the same time she is quite fearless as shown in her Outlast 2 and in late parts of DEVOUR collab  Kaela and Kobo. Even refusing to get backseated unless she is really lost, disliking hime-plays and stream snipes like in APEX streams.
        </item>
        <item>
            Kaela Kovalskia (カエラ・コヴァルスキア) is a female Indonesian Virtual YouTuber associated with hololive, debuting as part of its Indonesian (ID) branch third generation of VTubers alongside Vestia Zeta and Kobo Kanaeru.\n\nAfter taking over her great blacksmithing teacher\'s forge, she felt a lack of excitement in her life.So, she decided to be free and depart on a journey to find rare smithing materials, one of which was rumored to be under the building of a certain \"idol group\" in town.She also loves challenging herself and has a peculiar taste when it comes to foods!\n\nKaela appears to be a pretty calm person. She barely raises the voice even when she becomes angry. Kaela is known for her particular laugh, as she always laughs silently. She likes flirting a little with her chat as well and other VTubers like Vestia Zeta. Kaela also likes to tease other people. Despite admiring Ouro Kronii more than any one else within hololive, Kaela likes to compete with her at any opportunity. On the other hand, when people send back her compliments and kindness by telling her she is cute, Kaela stalls in a deny.\n\nKaela is an obsessional video game player. Among all hololive members, she stands on top for the longest average stream time. Frequently, she extends her gaming streams in order to do her favorite activity, which she calls \"grinding\". Most of her colleagues have learned after some time to acknowledge Kaela as a frightening worker when it comes to farming and getting experience on certain video games, which led to them regularly calling her as an impromptu gaming collab partner, even if it is just for emotional support. Despite these numerous requests, Kaela is always patient and happy to help, with patience being one of her strongest qualities. Following Moona\'s lessons on Minecraft, Kaela\'s dedication and experience earned her a strong reputation in all hololive. Thus, many Japanese members started calling her a god.\n\nShe exhibits many personalities, with one of the most popular being a little sister personality called "Ckia", taking a cute high pitched. Her next personality, Skia, sounds like an older sister and is supposed to be more skilled than Kaela, having a slightly deeper voice and a more audible laugh. Sometimes, Kaela can also adopt an old lady voice to become the one named \"Grandmaela\". She calls herself "Goriela" when she starts imitating gorilla noises, or even \"Omela\" while taking a deep male voice.\n\nLike Anya Melfissa, Kaela is very resistant to horror situations and never appears to be frightened. Additionally, her reaction to most horror scenarios (such as jump scares) has drawn comparisons to Shishiro Botan, where they laughed at situations that would otherwise scare their colleagues. For this reason, some of her colleagues called her as emotional support during their horror game streams, the most notable example being Hakos Baelz and Ceres Fauna on their The Mortuary Assistant stream.\n\nKaela shows sometimes a seductive side towards other hololive members. She likes to invite them all becoming her \"wives,\" as if she was grinding for a harem. This behavior led her being nicknamed "Elagator."
        </item>
        <item>
            Nekoyama Sena is an Indonesian female Virtual YouTuber affiliated with Yume Reality alongside Nemutaka Yuta, Tsuyu Hortenshia, Cerys Lobelia and Ryuuki Tatsuya.Sena is the result of a successful cat-human merger experiment by a Japanese company. But the government did not agree and wanted to destroy Sena.\n\nThe company\'s research team secretly created a tool to protect Sena from threats from the Japanese government. Without knowing it, this tool was a kind of time machine.Sena was carried away into the past, precisely to 2016. Sena was not teleported to her home country, Japan. Instead she was teleported to a country rich in spices, Indonesia. There she met a man who wanted to help him.\n\nSena is a very cheerful person and a bit hyperactive. She likes to joke with her audience and laughs a lot. Sena tries to be humorous, even if some of her jokes are a bit corny. Her fans generally really like her personality.\n\nShe has long white hair with an ahoge and pink hairbow with pink eyes and cat ears.
        </item>
        <item>
            Ayunda Risu (アユンダ・リス) is a female Indonesian Virtual YouTuber associated with hololive, debuting as part of its Indonesian (ID) branch first generation of VTubers alongside Airani Iofifteen and Moona Hoshinova.\n\nRisu has a humorous, high-energy and extremely friendly personality, not unlike Inugami Korone. According to herself she can be described as cheerful, clumsy and a crybaby. Risu\'s interactions with Moona and Iofi, other hololive members and anyone in general, have given her the reputation of being exceedingly sweet, kind and personable; as well as silly and mischievous. Risu support her friends so much some hololive ID members see her like a great sister. She is shown to be determined, as although she is bad with ghosts and horror games, she will still play them if her viewers request them, although she will scream and probably cry.\n\nWhile kind, she is very strict on the conduct of the live chat--frequently muting or bonking viewers. On more than one occasion she has taken time out of the stream to lecture misbehaving viewers. She is very concerned with making sure all Risuners are treated equally and does not give preferential treatment in bonking.\n\nRisu is also known for her randomness. For example, she made multitudes of 2-5 second long videos uploaded to her channel that consist of single words, phrases, or noises. She also had a stream where all she did was whistle and another that consisted of her counting coins from Moona\'s piggybank. Risu is notably talented for making lewd jokes or referencing memes on the same tone. This habit doesn\'t prevent her from behaving mature and calling her fans to stay reasonable.\n\nHer voice is the main trait to discern which of her two personalities is expressing. Under Risu\'s, the squirrel, her voice is particularly high pitched. However, under Ayunda\'s personality, she is perceived like a very seductive person because of her incredibly charming voice, making her sounding more mature.
        </item>
        <item>
            Moona Hoshinova (ムーナ・ホシノヴァ) is a female Indonesian Virtual YouTuber associated with hololive, debuting as part of its Indonesian (ID) branch first generation of VTubers alongside Airani Iofifteen and Ayunda Risu.\n\nIn her introduction stream, Moona introduced herself as a shy and quiet girl, which is the opposite of her image of a flat-faced college girl despite the fact she still speaks in an upbeat tone and a rather unique Indonesian accent. In the months following her debut, she rapidly developed into a more confident, upbeat talent. Moona often refers to herself as two souls sharing the same body: "Moona," the human aspect who speaks normally, and "Hoshinova," the moon goddess aspect who speaks in a lower pitch and shows a much more ominous, malevolent, and provocative personality.\n\nMoona has been shown to be a fast learner when it comes to new games, and it is not uncommon for her to go quiet in the middle of a stream to focus on gameplay. She has an eye for detail, and will often take her time to make sure she\'s doing something exactly as she wants it.\n\nShe is known to have a large appetite, frequently eating snacks on stream and talking about food, with cheeseburgers being a favorite of she and her fans. Moona is also known for her presence on Twitter, often interacting with fans, as well as posting spontaneous thoughts and observations with the hashtag "#RandoMoona".\n\nLike Tsunomaki Watame, she loves to bob and weave her head and body around. She loves to shitpost on Twitter while trying to connect with her fans. Moona is fond of teasing and flirting with her chat and other hololive members.\n\nMoona\'s ability to make others laugh gave her the reputation of being a comedian, but she jumps on any occasion to force people telling she rather is an idol.\n\nShe became renown before hololive for her experience at Minecraft, and so many members call for her help. In such case, Moona brings to them both resources and workforce. This aura reflected later on Kaela Kovalskia after Moona taught her.
        </item>
        <item>
            IpoChan was a female Indonesian Virtual YouTuber. She\'s debuted on 6 June 2018.\nIpoChan was a moe personification or gijinka of Internet Positif, an Indonesian web filtering service commonly used by major internet service providers in Indonesia, mainly to censor web content the Indonesian government deems inappropriate and/or immoral.\n\nIpoChan was originally revealed in July 2015 by Indonesian doujin circle Spring Roll, albeit her name was spelled Ipo-chan. The character became popular in Indonesia the same month. However, she did not debut as a virtual YouTuber until 6 June 2018.\n\nAccording to Social Blade statistics, all videos on her channel were privated in July 2021. As of January 2022, her Twitter account has been deleted, but her Instagram remains up.
        </item>
        <item>
            Mythia Batford (ミシア ・バットフォード) is an Indonesian female Virtual YouTuber. She uses both Indonesian and English on her stream.\nMythia is a calm person, although sometimes when she speaks, she can be funnier or more sadistic in her talks. She\'s been a couple of times talking about something weird and not true. However, she was flattered by some of her fans for her natural and good voice.\n\nShe has slightly asymmetrical short, light purple hair with mini bat-wing \'horns\' sticking out of her head. Her eyes are hot pink and she has a couple pink hairpins and an earring.\n\nHer YouTube channel was created on 15 October 2020. Her Twitter account was also created in the same month as the creation of her YouTube channel. On 1 December 2020, she debuted on Youtube.
        </item>
        <item>
            Airani Iofifteen (アイラニ・イオフィフティーン) is a female Indonesian Virtual YouTuber associated with hololive, debuting as part of its Indonesian (ID) branch first generation of VTubers alongside Moona Hoshinova and Ayunda Risu.\n\nIofi is a cute, cheerful and open person, but she is prone to panicking when things don\'t go in her favor or unexpected event happened on her streams. She has exceptional knowledge of Indonesian customs, slang and regional dialects. Her design also speaks for herself as a skilled artist who is currently majoring in VCD. She is energetic and talkative throughout her streams, and is quite open about her thoughts and feelings.\n\nHer streams are often described as calm and \"comfy,\" mixing her gameplay with chatting with the viewers, and has stated her love for free talks. She has a strong comedic side, often playing along with or against viewers. She never wavers from her views and values, and she plans each stream with the goal of a comfortable, engaging, and enjoyable experience with the viewer, whether that be through her collabs, content choice, or discussions. Her chats are varied and will often choose topics from the viewers, though she is quite passionate about talking on beauty/skin care, voice actors, gacha, and anime, with her favorite anime being One Piece.\n\nAmong hololive ID, Iofi is known for one of their most down bad members, capable to make very provoking but comical situations. Even Ayunda Risu seems sometimes more reasonable than Iofi. Moreover, Iofi is known for her great love of Monster Hunter franchise. She frequently tries to draw hololive members into some \"Moonhun\" collab.\n\nShe is incredibly supportive and social in general with a variety of personalities thanks to her knowledge of multiple languages and compassionate nature. She is very close with genmates Moona and Risu, streaming monthly together in collabs known as \"Area 15,\" with Iofi acting as Moona\'s \"husband\" and Risu\'s \"papa.\" Her nature during streams shifts between caring and flirtatious, with fans often calling her \"Erofi\" due to her antics, contrasting with the wholesome advice she often gives others. This advice is not restricted to VTubers; she has posted short videos encouraging viewers as well, and in general she is quite vocal and responsive to the chat during streams.\n\nShe collabs regularly with various groups members outside of Area 15, including "Kira Kira Family" with Risu, Aragami Oga, and Arurandeisu, and \"HoloFOI\" with Shirakami Fubuki and Oga. She and Tokino Sora, whom she calls \"Sora-neesan\" host a monthly show \"IoSoRadio\" on \"Otaku Talk.\" She frequently hosts one-on-one collabs both inside and outside of hololive, most commonly with Tsunomaki Watame, Ninomae Ina\'nis, Aisha, and Pochimaru. Due to her friendship with Pochimaru, Iofi is referred to by Pavolia Reine as \"tante Iofi\" or \"Auntie Iofi.\" She has also served as a \"bridge\" between personalities, helping them connect, such as Usada Pekora and Moona, and Yukoku Roberu and Ono Yuuki.\n\nWhile not the shortest in hololive, she was made fun of by Moona about how short she is; as such she is particularly sensitive when called short by others. When attempting to praise or compliment chat, they often turn around and complement her back. Though often calm, she can be prone to frustration, especially when it comes to gacha games or rhythm games, for the latter staying on the same song over and over until she is satisfied.
        </item>
        <item>
            Aika Meru was a female Virtual Youtuber, affiliated with Chapter 2 of Yume Reality with Keroro Suika and Koguma Keiya. Meru can speak Indonesian, English and a little bit of Japanese.\nShe has short, light pinkish hair with low hairbuns and panda ears, with golden eyes and a bamboo and panda shaped hairpins. She has a star shaped necklace.\n\nOn 5 September, Yume Reality announced Jolly Jungle\'s graduation. Aika Meru and Koguma Keiya will be graduated on 30 September and Keroro Suika on 3 October.
\n\nOn 28 September, the two remaining members of Jolly Jungle, Meru and Keiya held their graduation streams on their own channels.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_photo">
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/virtualyoutuber/images/3/3b/Kobo_Kanaeru_Portrait.png/revision/latest?cb=20220324054528</item>
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/virtualyoutuber/images/b/b6/Vestia_Zeta_Portrait.png/revision/latest?cb=20220324053909</item>
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/virtualyoutuber/images/6/61/Kaela_Kovalskia_Portrait.png/revision/latest?cb=20220324054230</item>
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/virtualyoutuber/images/f/f9/Nekoyama_Sena_Potrait.png/revision/latest?cb=20210114004617</item>
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/virtualyoutuber/images/d/de/Ayunda_Risu_-_Portrait.png/revision/latest?cb=20200427142410</item>
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/virtualyoutuber/images/9/94/Moona_Hoshinova_Portrait.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20200411161426</item>
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/virtualyoutuber/images/c/c3/Ipo_Chan_2.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20180922132437</item>
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/virtualyoutuber/images/5/53/Mythia_Batford_-_Portrait_2.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20220522075803</item>
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/virtualyoutuber/images/c/cb/Airani_Iofifteen_-_Portrait.png/revision/latest?cb=20200427135833</item>
        <item>https://static.wikia.nocookie.net/virtualyoutuber/images/b/b2/Aika_Meru.png/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/230?cb=20220114061805</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string name="question">How Do You Feel About This Article?</string>
    <string name="greeting">😊</string>
    <string name="love">💖</string>
    <string name="sad">🥺</string>
    <string name="count">13</string>

</resources>